



# JORDÃO NHANGA DE OLIVEIRA

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

(+244) 949 533 505 🕜 jordaonhanga7@gmail.com 🎁 Jordao de Oliveira

# JordaoNhanga15 www.jordaooliveira.dev

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Experienced software developer specializing in systems development, testing and maintenance. I have the ability to effectively self-manage independent projects and collaborate in productive teams. Experience in a variety of sectors, including Finance, Telecommunications and Real Estate, with a diverse set of skills.

#### SKILLS

- Teamwork and Influence;
- Leadership and Resilience;
- Creative and analytical thinking;
- Problem solving;
- Programming (C#, Javascript, Node.Js, SQL, Docker, MongoDB);
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Access).

#### LANGUAGES

- Portuguese Native and Fluent
- English Intermediate
- French Basic

#### ACTIVITIES

- Secretary for information, advertising and marketing.
  - I develop communication strategies
  - Advertising and Marketing Management
  - Internal Communications

# COURSES

- Node.js Application Developer Certification The **Linux Foundation**
- Web Development Course BUKA
- O Digital Entrepreneurship Course BUKA
- REST APIs Development Course UDEMY
- Neurolinguistic Programming Course ITGest **Training Center**
- Reverse Engineering, Memory Hacking and software Protection course - UDEMY
- O Developing Secure Software course LFD 121 The linux Foundation

# EXPERIENCE

#### **ITGEST**

Senior Software Engineer • Set 2024 - actual

- I worked as one of the software developers for the national banking regulator, where I participated directly in the project and gained valuable experience in the banking sector and the specific requirements of this type of application.
- I was responsible for implementing Angular and Cypress in all the company's projects, ensuring efficient automated testing and continuous integration. In addition, I contributed to the development of the standard architecture, ensuring the scalability of the applications.

#### Full Software Engineer • Jun 2022 - Ago 2024

• I wrote well-structured and readable code, aligned with the style guide, and delivered ETL software used for data collection in the national telecommunications sector, representing a significant milestone for my career.

#### EJunior Software Engineer • Fev 2021 — Jun 2022

• I took part in the development of software for the executive's project monitoring unit, being responsible for preparing reports on the platform, which were sent directly to the President of the Republic.

#### **PAYWI**

Frontend programmer • Jan 2021 — Mar 2021

• With my front-end experience, I contributed to the development of the startup, being responsible for implementing the layout and developing the front-end code.

#### **IMOOLIVEIRA**

System Administrator • Jul 2020 — Dez 2020

• At IMO OLIVEIRA, which operates in the real estate sector, I was responsible for the digital transformation, modernizing the company and maintaining the website, taking it from an archaic structure to a current and efficient operation.

#### NAELPRI

Programming trainer • Maio 2020 — Ago 2020

• I've been a programming trainer in various programming languages such as JavaScript, C# and SQL.

### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

#### **Computer Engineering**

Technical University of Angola • 2019-Actual

I'm in my 4th year of Computer Engineering

#### Namíbia Business Innovation Institute

NUST Namibia • Set de 2024 — Out 2024

• English language and communication.

## Santa Ana College and Noesa

High School • Jan 2016 — Dez 2018

Completed high school course in physical and biological sciences